<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- <string-array name="menu_item_left">
        <item>@string/how_to_use_app</item>
        <item>@string/Share_Application</item>
        <item>@string/faq</item>
        <item>@string/About_Healthcare_Saving_Card</item>
        <item>@string/About_National_Drug_Card</item>
    </string-array> -->
    
    <string-array name="array_string_faqs_questions">
        <item>How does the digital Rx card work?</item>
        <item>Who can benefit from this drug card?</item>
        <item>Can the members of my family also use this prescription drug discount card?</item>
        <item>How much will I save with the card?</item>
        <item>What prescription medications are covered under the National Drug Card Prescription benefit?</item>
        <item>Are there any age or enrollment restrictions?</item>
        <item>Can Anyone use the card?</item>
        <item>I am not a U.S. Citizen, can I use the card?</item>
        <item>Does my doctor need to know about this card when writing my prescription?</item>
        <item>Do prices vary among participating pharmacies?</item>
        <item>Why don’t all pharmacies accept the card?</item>
        <item>What if my pharmacist said the card would not save me any money?</item>
        <item>I already have insurance that covers my prescription drugs. How can this Drug Card benefit me?</item>
        <item>Can I search for a particular medication price on the app?</item>
        <item>Who should I contact if I have a problem with my pharmacy discount program?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="array_string_faqs_questions_items">
        <item>Simply give the card to the pharmacist and they will enter the codes in to their computer system. 
			The card holder then becomes a member of one of Largest Rx Buying Groups in America. As a 
			member, you have access to discounted prescription prices. Remember, with this card there are 
			no deductibles, no fees, no paper work or forms to complete, everyone qualifies. This program 
			covers your entire household and it is pre-activated and can be used immediately.</item>
        <item>            • Those with no insurance \n
			• Those who may have insurance but have limitations like high deductibles, non-covered drugs, 
			high copayments or caps on their benefits \n
			• Seniors who fall into the donut hole of their Medicare Part D \n
			• Employees who are in their waiting period for healthcare coverage \n
			• Employees who cannot afford COBRA payments when they lose their job \n
			• Employees who cannot afford to cover dependents \n</item>
        <item>Yes. This card will cover all of the family members living in your home.</item>
        <item>Savings of 10 to 85 on Brand-Name and Generic drugs. You will save an average of 8 times out of 10 over the pharmacy price. Take your prescription with your cards to a participating pharmacy and the pharmacist can tell you how much the medicine will cost with and without the use of the card.</item>
        <item>All FDA approved brand and generic prescription medications are covered.</item>
        <item>No, everyone can enroll and benefit.</item>
        <item>Yes, just use the share options located in the side menu to send the app to anyone. The side 
			menu can be accessed by pressing the menu button on the upper left corner of the app screen.</item>
        <item>Yes anyone may use the program if it is used at pharmacies within the U.S. and it s territories.</item>
        <item>            No. This program will not affect the way you are cared for by your physician. You should,
			however, always consult with your doctor about saving money on prescription medications.</item>
        <item>            Industry standards determine the discounted rate for prescription medications. This means in 
			most instances, all participating pharmacies will offer the same low price. These rates are 
			updated at least once a week, so prices may vary depending on when you go to the pharmacy. 
			From time-to-time, pharmacies may offer special sale prices for a limited time on selected 
			drugs. These sale prices may be lower than the scheduled discount rates, in which case the 
			card holder will pay only the lowered sales price. We always encourage comparison shopping.</item>
        <item>            All chain pharmacies and most independent pharmacies have been given equal opportunity to 
			serve you via this program. Pharmacies are required to offer very deep discounts and assist in 
			performing some fairly complicated drug management procedures on behalf of our card holders, 
			and some pharmacies simply refuse. However that gives you the confidence of knowing that 
			pharmacies participating have your best interests in mind and that there are the majority of 
			pharmacies in your regional area accept your card.</item>
        <item>As a member, you are entitled to your benefit. Your pharmacist will not know what the card
			savings will be until the prescription is sent for pricing through the pharmacist s computer. If your 
			Pharmacist does not want to comply with the program, you should consider going to another 
			nearby pharmacy that honors the card.</item>
        <item>			    This program can be used to obtain savings on prescription drugs that are excluded by your
				insurance plan or are not covered because you have exceeded your insurance plan s maximum 
				limits. In some instances, you might find that the Card s price is lower than your program s co-
				payment amount, but not usually. In addition, if your plan does not offer you a drug card and you 
				are reimbursed after each transaction, you may be able to use the Card to lower your out-of-
				pocket expenses.</item>
        <item>			    To search for how much a medication will cost on the app, follow these 3 easy steps. \n
		STEP 1: \n \n
		Press the “Search Prices” button on the bottom right corner of the app to access the National 
		Drug Card Rx Price search engine. \n
		STEP 2: \n \n
		Type in the name of your medication and and select the dosage and form from the drop pop up 
		list. \n
		STEP 3: \n \n
		Enter your zip code and press the Search button \n</item>
        <item>Call the Rx Help Desk 1 877 684 0032</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="app_name">Rx Card</string>
    <string name="desp">desp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Use_Free_Card">Use Free Card</string>
    <string name="Search_Prices">Search Prices</string>
    <string name="Free_RX_Card">Free Rx Card</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_app">How to Use App</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_digital_rx_card">How to Use Digital Rx Card</string>
    <string name="Share_Application">Share Application</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQs</string>
    <string name="links">Links</string>
    <string name="About_Healthcare_Saving_Card">About Healthcare Saving Club</string>
    <string name="share_message"><u>Save up to 85% on your medications with this NEW Free app and help my organization. Use the
									Group ID code: (group ID goes here) to activate the app. Share this app with all your friends and 
									family. 
									
									Download on iTunes http://grouprxapp.com/download
									Download on iTunes http://grouprxapp.com/download/google</u></string>
    <string name="Prices_And_Locations">Prices and Locations</string>
    <string name="enter_Group_ID">Enter Group ID :</string>
    <string name="Group_ID">Group ID</string>
    <string name="Group_text">Use the ID provided by your organization to activate the Free app. Your organization will benefit each time you use the GroupRx app at your local pharmacy.</string>
    <string name="activate_app">Activate App</string>
    <string name="Group_text_2">If you do not have a Group ID, press the button below to use the Free GroupRx app at your local pharmacy to save on your medications.</string>
    <string name="i_dont_have_group_id">I dont have a Group ID</string>
    <string name="Select_your_Card">Select Your Card</string>
    <string name="use_rx_card">Use Rx Card</string>
    <string name="use_rx_card_free_10_85_1">Save 10% - 85% on Brand-Name and Generics</string>
    <string name="about_free_pet_drug_card">About the Free Pet Drug Card</string>
    <string name="pet_card_info">The Free Pet Drug Card allows you to save money on most pet medications with just a click.
         		Since about 95 of the medication that we give to pets is only a different dosage of the medicine we take ourselves,
         		rather than spending more buying marked-up drugs from your Vet, you can give your furry friend the medicine they need at the pharmacy price.
         		All you need is a Free Pet Drug Card and a written prescription from your Vet to save up to 85% on drugs for your dog, cat or other pet. \n \n
				When you go to the vet and pay for medicine, you are overpaying on wholesale markups simply to get a different dosage of medicine
				available at any participating pharmacy. The Free Pet Drug Card allows you to get the right drug for your pet and save up to 85. \n \n
				To take advantage of our Free Pet Drug Card, all you need to do is present this card to your pharmacist. There is no expiration date,
				no limit to usages and no paperwork to fill out. The card is accepted in 63,000 pharmacies across the nation to get you the best deal on prescriptions.</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="Donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="About_National_Drug_Card">About National Drug Card</string>
    <string name="About_National_Drug_Card_Content">Founded in 2005, National Drug Card is a Washington, D.C. based organization that offers
        	 a free discount drug card to millions of people across the United States and its territories allowing 
        	 them save money on their prescription medications. Anyone is eligible for the card, but it especially benefits 
        	 those with no health insurance, senior citizens, small business owners, families, college students, the unemployed 
        	 and the undocumented. Additionally, individuals who have prescription benefits can use NDC to receive discounts 
        	 on medications that are not covered by their insurance plan or those seniors who Medicare Part D, you may be at 
        	 risk of falling into the prescription drug coverage gap, or doughnut hole.</string>
    <string name="NDC_Savings_Club_Page">NDC Savings Club Page</string>
    <string name="About_NDC_Content">National Drug Card recently launched the nation’s first Healthcare Savings Club.
         		This new program offers more than 75 types of savings and preferred pricing, with discounts on medical,
         		 dental, vision, labs, podiatry, diabetes, hearing, legal, travel, shopping, entertainment and more.
         		  We also have sections for holistic &amp; natural treatments as well as resources for seniors, men and women.
         		   The NDC Savings Club’s mission is to enhance the quality of life for families, groups, businesses,
         		    non-profits and organizations by providing a free online directory dedicated 
         		    to helping them cut their healthcare costs.</string>

    <string name="PLS_SELECT_GROUPID">Please Insert GroupID</string>

</resources>